Register to The Karl Weigl Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, Series I
  - Music by Karl Weigl, I.A
    - Orchestral music
      - [Symphonisch Vorspiel zu einer Tragödie]
        - Symphonic prelude to a tragedy / Karl Weigl. Composers Facsimile Edition / American Composers Alliance (New York City)., 1 manuscript score (70 p.); 35 cm. (Box 14, Folder 416)
    - Chamber Music
      - [Bagatelles, violins (4), piano]
        - Four short pieces for four clarinets or four violins and piano / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (8 p.); 41 cm. (Box 31, Folder 1034)
        - [Bagatelles, violins (4), piano] (Box 31, Folder 1035)
          Alternatively for four clarinets or for "flute, violin, clarinet, and violoncello."
      - [Bagatelles, violins (4), piano. Parts]
        - Four bagatelles for 4 violins or woodwind quartet / Karl Weigl. New York: John Markert, c1956., 4 parts; 33 cm. (Box 15, Folder 417)
          Parts for four violins.
          Photocopy.
      - [Bagatelles, violins (4), piano; arr.]
        - Four bagatelles for woodwind quintet and piano / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (8 p.); 44 cm. + 5 manuscript parts; 37 cm. (Box 31, Folder 1036)
          Originally for four violins and piano; arranged for wind quintet (flute, oboe, clarinet, horn, and bassoon) and piano.
      - [Bagatelles, violins (4), piano; arr. Parts]
        - Four bagatelles for woodwind quintet / Karl Weigl., 5 manuscript parts; 37 cm. (Box 15, Folder 418)
          Photocopy of undated manuscript parts for flute, oboe, clarinet, horn, and bassoon, c1972.
      - [Bagatelles, violins (4), piano. Norwegian dance; arr.]
      - [Intermezzi, string quartet]
        - 3 intermezzi / by Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (7 p.); 43 cm. (Box 31, Folder 1037)
      - [Intermezzi, string quartet; arr.]
        - Little suite for strings: three intermezzi: (for strin[g] quintet or string orchestra) / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (7 p.); 44 cm. (Box 31, Folder 1038)
          Originally for string quartet; arranged for 2 violins, viola, violoncello, and double bass.
          Title from caption altered in manuscript.
        - [Intermezzi, string quartet; arr.] (Box 31, Folder 1039)
          Alternatively for "flute, oboe, clarinet, 2 bassoons, and french horn."
        - Intermezzi for strings / by Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (9 p.); 35 cm. (Box 15, Folder 419)
          "Musicians Edition."
          Originally for string quartet; arr. for 2 violins, viola, violoncello, and double bass.
        - [Intermezzi, string quartet; arr.] (Box 15, Folder 420)
          Title of Part I changed from "New Day" to "Revelation" in manuscript.
        - [Intermezzi, string quartet; arr.] (Box 15, Folder 421)
          "c1947, Whitney Blake Music Publishers, N.Y.C."
          Parts I and II only.
          Title of Part I changed from from "New Day" to "Meditation" and "Revelation" in manuscript.
        - [Intermezzi, string quartet; arr.] (Box 15, Folder 422)
          Composers Facsimile Edition. c1966 / American Composers Alliance (New York City).
          Part I titled "New Day."
      - [Intermezzi, string quartet; arr. Parts]
        - 3 intermezzi for string quartet / Karl Weigl., 4 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 15, Folder 423)
          Photocopy of undated manuscript parts for violin, viola, violoncello, and double bass.
          "Karl Weigl" changed on some parts to "Shangri-La" in manuscript.
        - New day; Capriccio; Interrupted serenading / Karl Weigl. Composers Facsimile Edition, c1966 / American Composers Alliance (New York City)., 5 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 424)
          Photocopy of manuscript parts.
      - [Intermezzi, string quartet. Revelation; arr. Parts]
        See also Keyboard Music
        - New day: intermezzo no. 1 / Karl Weigl. New York: Whitney Blake Music Publishers, c1947., 5 manuscript parts; 31 cm. (Box 15, Folder 426)
          Title changed form "New Day" to "Revelation" in manuscript.
      - [Intermezzi, string quartet. Capriccio; arr. Parts]
        - Capriccio: 2. intermezzo / Karl Weigl. New York: Whitney Blake Music Publishers, c1947., 5 manuscript parts; 31 cm. (Box 15, Folder 427)
      - [Intermezzi, string quartet. Interrupted serenading; arr. Parts]
        - Interrupted serenading: intermezzo no. 3 / Karl Weigl. New York: Whitney Blake Music Publishers, c1947., 5 manuscript parts; 31 cm. (Box 15, Folder 428)
      - [Love song]
        See [Pieces, violoncello, piano. Love song; arr.]
      - [Lullaby]
        See [Pictures from childhood. Lullaby]
      - [Minuet, violoncello, piano]
        - Menuetto for violoncello and piano / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (4 p.) + 1 part ([2] p.); 34 cm. (Box 15, Folder 429)
        - Menuetto for violoncello and piano / Karl Weigl. New York: John Markert, c1956., 1 score (4 p.) + 1 part ([2] p.); 32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 430)
        - Fragment of cello part for Menuetto for violoncello and piano., 1 manuscript fragment (1 sheet); 31 cm. (Box 15, Folder 431)
      - [Pictures from childhood]
        - Pictures from childhood: four miniatures for flute (or violin) and piano / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (6 p.) + 1 part (2 p.); 36 cm. (Box 15, Folder 432)
        - [Pictures from childhood] (Box 15, Folder 433)
          Same photocopy as above (flute part only).
        - [Pictures from childhood] (Box 15, Folder 434)
        - Pictures from childhood: four miniatures for flute (or violin) and piano / Karl Weigl., 1 score (15 p.) + 1 part (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 15, Folder 435)
          S. l.: Boosey and Hawkes, c1969.
          Plate no.: B. W. I. 232.
      - [Pictures from childhood. Lullaby]
        - Lullaby for flute (recorder) or violin and piano / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 27 cm. (Box 15, Folder 436)
          "Karl Weigl" changed to "Yosemite" in manuscript.
      - [Pieces, violin, piano]
        - Two pieces for violin and piano / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score ([6] p.) + 1 part (2 p.); 35 cm. (Box 15, Folder 437)
      - [Pieces, violoncello, piano, op. 33]
        - Two pieces for violoncello and piano / by Karl Weigl. Reproduced by Independent Music Publishers (New York City)., 1 manuscript score (14 p.); 33 cm. + 1 part (5 p.); 34 cm. (Box 15, Folder 438)
        - Two pieces for violoncello and piano / Karl Weigl. New York: Arrow Music Press, c1943., 1 score (14 p.); + 1 part (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 15, Folder 439)
        - Two pieces for violoncello and piano / Karl Weigl. New York: Arrow Music Press, c1943., 1 score (14 p.); + 1 part (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 15, Folder 440)
          Score annotated in manuscript.
      - [Pieces, violoncello, piano, op. 33. Love song. arr.]
        - Love song / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript part (1 sheet); 35 cm. (Box 15, Folder 441)
          Part originally for cello; arranged for tenor saxophone in B-flat.
          Photocopy of an undated manuscript part.
      - [Sonata, viola, piano]
        - Sonata for viola and piano, opus 38 / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (29 p.) + 1 part (9 p.); 31 cm. (Box 15, Folder 442)
          "Edited by Nadia Reisenberg"-- in manuscript.
        - Sonata for piano and viola / Karl Weigl; edited by Nadia Reisenberg. New York: John Markert, c1953., 1 score (29 p.) + 1 part (9 p.); 32 cm. (Box 15, Folder 443)
          "Edited by Paul Doktor"-- viola part.
        - [Sonata, viola, piano] (Box 15, Folder 444)
          With a photocopy of an undated manuscript part.
      - [Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 16, C major]
        - Sonate, Violine und Klavier, Opus 16 / Karl Weigl. Mainz: B. Schott's Söhne, c1924., 1 score (43 p.) + 1 part (16 p.); 33 cm. (Box 15, Folder 445)
          Plate no.: 31141.
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 16, C major] (Box 15, Folder 446)
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 16, C major] (Box 16, Folder 447)
      - [Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 2, G major]
        - Sonata for violin and piano (G-major) / Karl Weigl. Composers Facsimile Edition. c1958 / American Composers Alliance (New York City)., 1 manuscript score (39 p.) + 1 part (11 p.); 35 cm. (Box 16, Folder 448)
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 2, G major] (Box 16, Folder 449)
          Part annotated in manuscript.
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 2, G major] (Box 16, Folder 450)
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 2, G major] (Box 16, Folder 451)
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 2, G major] (Box 16, Folder 453)
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 2, G major] (Box 16, Folder 454)
      - [Sonata, violoncello, piano]
        - Sonate für Violoncello und Klavier = Sonata for violoncello and piano / by Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (37 p.) + 1 part (11 p.); 35 cm. (Box 16, Folder 455)
          "Facsimile Edition" -- in manuscript.
          Manuscript fingerings and bowings in cello part by Marcel Hubert.
        - [Sonata, violoncello, piano] (Box 17, Folder 456)
        - [Sonata, violoncello, piano] (Box 17, Folder 457)
          Same photocopy as above (violoncello part only).
        - Sonata for violoncello and piano, opus 41 / Karl Weigl. New York: John Markert, c1968., 1 violoncello part (11 p.); 27 cm. (Box 17, Folder 458)
      - [String quartets, no. 1, C minor, op. 20]
        - Streichquartett für 2 Violinen, Viola und Violoncell, op. 20 / Karl Weigl. Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel, c1926., 1 miniature score (67 p.); 20 cm. (Box 17, Folder 459)
          Publisher's no.: Partitur-Bibliothek Nr. 2665.
          Plate no.: 29475.
      - [String quartets, no. 1, C minor, op. 20. Parts]
        - Streichquartett für 2 Violinen, Viola und Violoncell, op. 20 / Karl Weigl. Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel, c1926., 4 parts; 31 cm. (Box 17, Folder 460)
          Publisher's no.: Edition Breitkopf 5318.
          Plate no.: 29476.
      - [String quartets, no. 2, E major]
        - II. Streichquartett (mit Viola d'amore) / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (28 p.); 28 x 34 cm. (Box 17, Folder 461)
        - [String quartets, no. 2, E major. Parts], 4 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 17, Folder 462)
          2. Streichquartet in E-Dur (mit Viola und Viola d'amore) / von Karl Weigl.
          Undated manuscript parts.
        - 2. Streichquartett in E-Dur für 2 Violinen, Viola (auch Viola d'amour) u. Violoncello / componirt von Karl Weigl., 4 manuscript parts; 36 cm. (Box 17, Folder 463-466)
          Photocopy of undated manuscript parts.
      - [String quartets no. 3, A major, op. 4. Parts]
        - Quartett, A-Dur, für 2 Violinen, Viola und Violoncell, op. 4 / von Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1911., 4 parts; 32 cm. (Box 17, Folder 467)
          Publisher's nos.: 2930, U. E. 2920a-d.
        - [String quartets no. 3, A major, op. 4. Parts] (Box 17, Folder 468)
          Bound in volume.
      - [String quartets, no. 4, D minor]
        - Streichquartett, d-Moll / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (37 p.); 34 cm. (Box 18, Folder 469)
        - [String quartets, no. 4, D minor] (Box 18, Folder 470)
        - IV. Streichquartett, d-Moll, für 2 Violinen, viola und Violoncell / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (57 p.); 34 cm. (Box 18, Folder 471)
        - [String quartets, no. 4, D minor] (Box 18, Folder 472)
          Joshua Corporation (Hastings-on-Hudson, NY), c19--.
      - [String quartets, no. 4, D minor. Parts]
        - Streichquartett, d-Moll / Karl Weigl., 4 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 18, Folder 473)
        - [String quartets, no. 4, D minor. Parts] (Box 18, Folder 474)
      - [String quartets, no. 4, D minor. Requiem for Eva]
        - Requiem für Eva / Karl Weigl., 1 ms.part fragment (1 p.); 36 cm. (Box 18, Folder 475)
          Fragment of a viola part from the third movement of his String Quartet no. 4.
        - [Notes about cuts for String quartet no. 4], 1 item (1 sheet); 22 cm. (Box 18, Folder 476)
          Manuscript notes written in an unidentified hand, undated.
      - [String quartets, no. 5, G major, op. 31]
        - Streichquartett, G-Dur, op. 31 = Quatour à cordes, sol maj. = String quartet, G maj. / Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1936., 1 miniature score (56 p.); 19 cm. (Box 18, Folder 477)
        - [String quartets, no. 5, G major, op. 31] (Box 18, Folder 478)
          "American Composers Edition" - stamp.
        - [String quartets, no. 5, G major, op. 31] (Box 18, Folder 479)
          "Im leichten (klassischen) Stil" -- in manuscript.
        - [String quartets, no. 5, G major, op. 31] (Box 18, Folder 480)
      - [String quartets, no. 5, G major, op. 31. Parts]
        - Streichquartett in leichtem Stil / Karl Weigl., 4 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 18, Folder 481)
        - Streichquartett, G-Dur, op. 31 / Karl Weigl. Austria: Universal Edition, c1936., 4 parts; 31 cm. (Box 19, Folder 482)
        - [String quartets, no. 5, G major, op. 31. Parts] (Box 19, Folder 483)
        - [String quartets, no. 5, G major, op. 31. Parts] (Box 19, Folder 484)
          Same edition as above (second violin part only).
        - [String quartets, no. 5, G major, op. 31. Parts] (Box 19, Folder 485)
        - [String quartets, no. 5, G major, op. 31. Parts] (Box 19, Folder 486)
      - [String quartets, no. 6, C major]
        - String-Quartet, C-Major, for 2 violins, viola, violoncello / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (30 p.); 38 cm. (Box 19, Folder 487)
          Photocopy of an undated manuscript score, copied by W. Weissleder, New York City.
          "Opus 37" -- in manuscript.
        - [String quartets, no. 6, C major] (Box 19, Folder 488)
          Same photocopy, with parts.
      - [String quartets, no. 7, F minor]
        - String quartet, F minor, for 2 violins, viola, and violoncello / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (34 p.); 38 cm. (Box 19, Folder 489)
        - [String quartets, no. 7, F minor] (Box 19, Folder 490)
        - [String quartets, no. 7, F minor] (Box 19, Folder 491)
        - [String quartets, no. 7, F minor] (Box 31, Folder 1040)
      - [String quartets, no. 7, F minor. Parts]
        - String quartet, F minor, for 2 violins, viola, and violoncello / Karl Weigl., 4 manuscript parts.; 36 cm. (Box 19, Folder 492)
        - [String quartets, no. 7, F minor. Parts] (Box 19, Folder 493)
      - [String quartets, no. 8, D major]
        - Eighth string quartet / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (42 p.); 38 cm. (Box 19, Folder 494)
        - [String quartets, no. 8, D major] (Box 19, Folder 495)
          Same photocopy as above (reduced).
        - [String quartets, no. 8, D major] (Box 19, Folder 496)
        - [String quartets, no. 8, D major] (Box 31, Folder 1041)
        - [String quartets, no. 8, D major] (Box 19, Folder 497)
        - [String quartets, no. 8, D major. Parts], 4 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 20, Folder 498)
          8th string quartet in D-Major / Karl Weigl.
        - [Trios, piano, strings] Composers Facsimile Edition, c1958 / American Composers Alliance (New York City). (Box 20, Folder 499)
        - Trio for violin, violoncello, and piano / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (44 p.); 34 cm. + 2 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 20, Folder 500)
          Composers Facsimile ed., c1958.
        - [String quartets, no. 8, D major] (Box 20, Folder 501)
          Annotations in manuscript by George Laslow.
    - Keyboard Music
      - [Bagatelles, violins (4), piano. Norwegian dance; arr.]
        - Norwegian dance: for piano duet / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 37 cm. (Box 20, Folder 502)
        - [Bagatelles, violins (4), piano. Norwegian dance; arr.] (Box 20, Folder 503)
          "Arranged for piano duet by V. Weigl" -- in manuscript.
        - [Bagatelles, violins (4), piano. Norwegian dance; arr.] (Box 20, Folder 504)
          Composers Facsimile Edition, c1939 / American Composers Alliance (New York City).
      - [Bilder und Geschichten]
        - Bilder und Geschichten: sechs Klavierstücke = Pictures and tales: six piano pieces: op. 2 / Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1937., 15 p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 20, Folder 505)
          Publisher's n.: U. E. 2796.
        - [Bilder und Geschichten] (Box 20, Folder 506)
          "Optional for flute and harpsichord" -- in manuscript.
          Annotations in manuscript indicating flute part.
      - [Fantasies, piano]
        - Six fantasies for piano / Karl Weigl. Composers Facsimile Edition, c1958 / American Composers Alliance (New York City)., 15 p. of manuscript music; 40 cm. (Box 20, Folder 507)
          Photocopy of an undated manuscript.
        - [Fantasies, piano] (Box 20, Folder 508)
          "Day Phantasies" -- in manuscript.
        - [Fantasies, piano] (Box 20, Folder 509)
          Same photocopy as above (nos. 2-6 only).
          "From Six Phantasies, 'Day Phantasies'" -- in manuscript.
        - [Fantasies, piano] (Box 20, Folder 510)
          Same photocopy as above (nos. 1-2 and part of no. 3
      - [Fantasies, piano. Capriccio; arr.]
        - Capriccio for piano duet / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 35 cm. (Box 20, Folder 511)
          Originally for piano solo.
      - [Intermezzi, string quartet. Revelation; arr.]
        - Revelation: for piano duet (4 hands) / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 36 cm. (Box 20, Folder 512)
          "Meditation" -- caption title.
        - [Intermezzi, string quartet. Revelation; arr.] (Box 20, Folder 513)
          Title changed to "Revelation" in manuscript.
      - [Nachtphantasien]
        - Nachtphantasien: op. 13 / Karl Weigl. Leipzig: F. E. C. Leuckart, c1922., 25 p. of music; 35 cm. (Box 20, Folder 514)
          For solo piano.
          Publisher's no.: F. E. C. L. 8154.
        - [Nachtphantasien] (Box 20, Folder 515)
      - [Nachtphantasien; arr.]
        - Night phantasies: for two pianos: op. 13 / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (15 p.); 39 cm. (Box 20, Folder 516)
          Nos. 1, 2, and 5 from Nachtphantasien, originally for solo piano.
        - [Nachtphantasien; arr.] (Box 20, Folder 517)
          "c1939."
        - [Nachtphantasien; arr.] (Box 20, Folder 518)
        - [Nachtphantasien; arr.] (Box 20, Folder 519)
        - [Old Vienna; arr.] Reproduced by Independent Music Publishers (New York City). (Box 20, Folder 520)
        - Tänze aus Wien = Dances from Vienna: for two pianos for four hands / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (32 p.); 34 cm. (Box 20, Folder 521)
          Originally for orchestra.
          "Old Vienna" -- added to caption in manuscript.
          Photocopy of a manuscript score copied by W. Weissleder, dated at New York, March 1939.
        - [Nachtphantasien; arr.] (Box 20, Folder 522)
          Caption title changed to "Tänze aus dem alten Wien" in manuscript.
        - [Nachtphantasien; arr.] (Box 21, Folder 524)
          Same photocopy, with caption title changed to Tänze aus dem alten Wien."
          "Vienna That Was" and "Old Vienna" -- added to caption in manuscript.
          Same photocopy as above (2 copies), with caption title changed to "Vienna that was: dances from old Vienna."
        - Dances from old Vienna: for piano, four hands / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (34 p.); 34 cm. (Box 21, Folder 525)
          Parts on facing pages.
      - [Passacaglias and fugues, organ, D minor]
        - Passacaglia und Fuge, d moll, für Orgel / Karl Weigl., 17 p. of manuscript music; 27 x 34 cm. (Box 21, Folder 526)
          Undated manuscript.
        - Passacaglia and fugue in D minor / Karl Weigl., 17 p. of manuscript music; 29 x 35 cm. (Box 21, Folder 527)
        - [Passacaglias and fugues, organ, D minor] (Box 21, Folder 528)
        - [Passacaglias and fugues, organ, D minor] (Box 21, Folder 529)
          "In the baroque style" -- in manuscript.
      - [Preludes and fugues, organ, C minor]
        - Prelude and Fugue: in the old style: C minor / Karl Weigl., 12 p. of manuscript music; 27 x 34 cm. (Box 21, Folder 530)
          Manuscript, with revisions.
        - Organ prelude and fugue, C minor: in the old style / Karl Weigl., 12 p. of manuscript music; 28 x 35 cm. (Box 21, Folder 531)
        - [Preludes and fugues, organ, C minor] (Box 21, Folder 532)
      - [Preludes and fugues, organ, D major]
        - Präludium und fuge für Orgel: im alten Stil / Karl Weigl., 16 p. of manuscript music; 28 x 37 cm. (Box 21, Folder 533)
      - [Tanz der Erinnyen]
        - Tanz der Erinnyen / Karl Weigl., 7 p. of manuscript music; 35 cm. (Box 21, Folder 534)
          "Dance of the Furies" -- in manuscript.
          "Corrected copy" -- in manuscript.
          Photocopy of an undated manuscript, with annotations.
        - [Tanz der Erinnyen] (Box 21, Folder 535)
        - [Tanz der Erinnyen] (Box 21, Folder 536)
          "Dance of the Furies."
        - [Tanz der Erinnyen] (Box 21, Folder 537)
        - [Tanz der Erinnyen] (Box 21, Folder 538)
      - [Variations, piano]
        - 28 Variationen über ein achttaktiges Thema, für Klavier zu zwei Händen, op. 15 / von Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1923., 13 p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 21, Folder 539)
          Publisher's no.: U. E. 6367.
          Photocopy with annotations in manuscript.
        - [Variations, piano] (Box 21, Folder 540)
          Same photocopy, with annotations.
    - Transcriptions
      - [Rondo capricioso; arr.], Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847
        - Rondo capriccioso: op. 14 / Felix Mendelssohn; transcr. for solo clarinet and orchestra by Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript part (4 p.); 33 cm. (Box 21, Folder 541)
          Originally for solo piano.
          Part for solo clarinet.
      - [Deux marches caractéristiques; arr.], Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828
        - Deux marches caractéristiques: op. 121 / Franz Schubert; Instr. [von Karl Weigl]., 1 manuscript score (2 v.) + 32 parts; 34 cm. (Box 21, Folder 542-543)
          Originally for piano duet; arranged for orchestra.
          Undated manuscript scores and parts.
          "Karl Weigl" changed to "Berkeley" on scores and some parts.
        - Deux marches caractéristiques: op. 121 / Franz Schubert; instr. v. Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (2 v.); 34 cm. (Box 21, Folder 544)
          Undated manuscript scores.
        - Deux marches caractéristiques: op. 121 / Franz Schubert; instr. v. Karl Weigl., 40 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 21, Folder 545)
          Undated manuscript parts for orchestra.
          "Karl Weigl" changed to "Berkeley" -- on some parts.
  - Music By Others, I.B
    - Precepts of Angelus Silesius: a cycle for 3-6 women's voices a capella / Ernst Bacon. Bennington, VT: Bennington College, c1957., Bacon, Ernst, 1898-1990; 1 score (13 p.); 27 cm. (Box 22, Folder 546)
      For two women's choirs.
      Publisher's no.: B.C.S. 4.
      "The works presented in this series were commissioned by Bennington College for its Graduation Ceremony ...."
    - Quiet airs / by Ernst Bacon. New York: Syracuse University Press; Mercury Music, c1952., Bacon, Ernst, 1898-1990; 1 score (23 p.); 28 cm. (Box 22, Folder 547)
      Song cycle.
      Inscribed to by Bacon to Vally Weigl.
    - [Songs. Selections] San Francisco: Ernst Bacon, c1928., Bacon, Ernst, 1898-1990; 1 score (35 p.); 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 548)
    - [Songs. Selections] New York: The New Music Society Publishers, 1942 Jan., Bacon, Ernst, 1898-1990; 1 score (15 p.); 28 cm. (Box 22, Folder 549)
      New Music: A Quarterly Publishing Modern Compositions (v. 15).
    - [Songs. Selections] San Francisco; Ernst Bacon, n.d., Bacon, Ernst, 1898-1990; 1 score ([18] p.); 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 550)
    - Lieder fernen gedenkens: op. posth. / von Evelyn Faltis. Berlin: Ries & Erler, n.d., Faltis, Evelyn; 1 score (11 p.); 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 551)
      Plate no.: R.10 209 E.
      Printed card "zum Gedächtinis an Evelyn Faltis," with an
      unidentified signature, laid in.
    - [Kinderstücke] Sechs Kinderstücke: für Klavier / von Paul Frankl., Frankl, Paul; 1 manuscript score ([27] p.); 34 cm. (Box 22, Folder 552)